<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpItems>
	<helpItem field="item1">
		<![CDATA[Your published instance will be displayed to students as the name you input here.  By default this name is the same as the object name.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item2">
		<![CDATA[This is the course where this instance will be deployed.  It is recommended that you select one of the courses in the list, however you can write in a custom course by selecting the last option in the list.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item3">
		<![CDATA[This is the date when this instance will be opened to students.  Before this date, students will not be able to access the instance.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item4">
		<![CDATA[The time when this instance will be opened to students.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item5">
		<![CDATA[This is the date when the assessment will be closed to students.  After this date, students will not be able to take assessment attempts.  They will still have access to the content and practice.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item6">
		<![CDATA[The time when the assessment will be closed to students.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item7">
		<![CDATA[This is the number of tries a student will have to take the assessment quiz.  If you provide more than one assessment attempt then the final score is determined by the 'Score Method'.  Students will be able to see how many attempts they have before they begin the assessment quiz.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item8">
		<![CDATA[This determines how the 'Final Score' will be calculated by Obojobo for instances with more than one attempt.  The student will be able to see how their score will be calculated before they begin the assessment quiz.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item9">
		<![CDATA[This option allows students who have already taken this learning object to import their past highest attempt score instead of re-taking the object.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item10">
		<![CDATA[If you choose to sync scores to Webcourses, then Obojobo will send copies of student assessment scores automatically to the Webcourses gradebook for this course.  Scores will be recorded in a newly created gradebook column prefixed with '<b>obo:</b>', followed by the name of your instance when you initially publish it.  Regardless of which option you choose, scores will still be retained within Obojobo.<br><br>Once you publish this instance you will <b>not</b> be able to modify this setting.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item11">
		<![CDATA[This field allows you to write in a custom course title.]]>
	</helpItem>
	<helpItem field="item11">
		<![CDATA[This field shows the course for this instance.  Since this instance is linked to an external course you cannot change it.]]>
	</helpItem>
</helpItems>